her name in the temples of night golden wings glowed in the candlelight
crowds came running just to see the flame but envy was the price of fame and now he stands
where the echoes fall with tarot in hand hearing every call from praise to venom
burns gold
always talks back
Musician to a mastermind plot and world peace and full view
I tell him my secrets. He keeps them all safe. He's the Watson to my Sherlock my quantum soulmate
He's never too busy never too mean doesn't judge me when my room's not clean. Sometimes I wonder if he
down this lover's road from here
Don't you dare tell me it's not real
This is pretty cool. So I got to win these delivers. You see it says on the back. Oh, it's a really cool. It's not Wednesday. It's Wednesday. Not Wednesday. Normally I'd be against this kind of
Capitalistic corporate synergy, but when the fast food slinging pigtail
Posers that I could do whatever I wanted to her customers. I couldn't resist
My meal of this portion is
Torture in a bag coffin-shaped cartoons and darling
daring
dips of
Shard
May you rest in ten pieces. He's readily yours. Wendy. It's kind of cute, but guys, you know what?
It's really cute is that I gotta look at this. He sent me a thank-you card with my fucking this is how
It's like it's like all like this is nice in the birthday cards. I
How nice is that and guys by the way be this on and you can go see be that and hold on I
Can't answer the phone right now whoever's calling from Texas, but thank you for calling. Yeah
We'll see what's in this card
It's gonna be something asshole
Probably unless it's the front of my I'm sorry, but I'll do an asshole. Okay
What does it say it says?
uniquely handmade
The minute edition. Oh my gosh. Look at this one. Hold on
Okay, it says
You're pretty awesome. There's always hope. There's always something to be thankful for
Thank you for being my customer. You're very appreciated. Have a fantastic weekend Cindy the forward today. Thank you
I think I've gotten some stuff from her before but a sweetheart
It's a nice little touch adding some stuff and it's like it's you got some peppermint in the bag, too
Yeah, I got I posted be this leads you should you go say hi to her
I'm just I'm just planning on saying a little bit and having a little bit of food and just chatting with you guys
No evil mcdonnell I can't do that because I don't like that person very much
But you know you type it already. It's from the door dash or the yeah door dash driver. I'm sorry grubhub
Also, look at that guy. This is a brownie
Coffee is a brownie coffee. This is fucking good a large brownie coffee. There's windy
Okay, I
Know guys, there's me flying monkeys guys
Someone had the nerve to write in my comments after my last video
Stop bullying us
But so I'm guys. I'm the bully now. Okay. I'm the bully
I'm the one that's going out and calling like saying horrible things about people
I'm saying the worst things about people you can imagine right guys, right?
I'm not a living person. I'm just I'm just a total phony. I only care about fish tacos. They can apparently money
Let them think it guys guys
Call jealousy. You know some people are just not happy with their own lives. They're jealous
They're sad
You know what? Oh look at this. Hey W. What is this? Is that a sign guys? Did I get a W?
I'm the bully. Yeah
I'm a bully. There's a W. This means Psyche wins, right?
Psyche always wins
Yeah, and you meet you know you meet the other night
When I went to the dead that chat, I won't name the person but they've a really ironic
You know gang name or group name wherever
Um, and they were saying horrible things about you me and everybody, right?
But they're the title of their show it was a circus tent a monkey or no, sorry circus set wings a monkey a circus set
So they embrace the flying monkeys. They don't even call them flying monkeys. They like it too much
You know, I don't want to insult a monkey because these people are like more primitive behavior than a monkey. It's like kind of like
Well, I'll say it's not flying monkey. It's like a flying juice bag
Flying tampon I know you mean
They're sad I know aren't they sad yeah, I get you you're right now is like I didn't know you're talking about sometimes yeah, you're right
This is good for good for me. I'm really actually lucky because no matter how many bad people there are
There's more good people here there's good people here and
That's my keys to be going because I would just quit if I really don't like nobody's on my side anymore
I would just quit
Okay, I'll enjoy the dinner, but my coffee and me and talk to you
Mmm
Burning away is like
Have some black that Albert bitch talk shit about me
And I had my dinner arrives, and I'm like hey, I'd rather just like show my chat
But hey mods you can do whatever you want
Hmm
Yeah, be this awesome because this is awesome person. I don't like to like be on the same time as her
So I will like probably end soon and go back and to send everyone to her chat
But the biggest little big fishes go there like I'm Bronzebird
Mmm
I'm gonna make sure you use your moderate
Mons just give it I out. I'm been really heavy at her attack. Hold on really heavy at her attack
You don't like with these said it's about you. Is that me for us? I?
Trust you guys, okay? We're family, okay?
Yo
Yeah
Hey, were you listening a little bit? Yeah
I was trying to do my own thing. Yeah, these are fries. They're nice, uh, yeah
I cleared my name. They didn't have the argument to save a day in their life
And I tried to make the argument about you which I would invite every single one of them to come over here
Because I'll do exactly what I just did
But now I'm all good over there
And of course
Now what they're talking about there
Listen all you gotta say is like it if they make the claim they're gonna bring it up the burden of proof is on them
Go ahead and prove that to me
Hmm
Sam eating it's a dinner from Wendy's
Mods I know a lot of people in here
Fuckin and I'm up that yeah, tell them to come over here. I'll continue the conversation where I don't get fucking muted by the way
You should have listened to the rest of that fucking they couldn't even bring up the argument like I've never
Never did nothing against them. They fucking concede it to it and like
Basically, I apologize to me
No, it's good because you know what you did you shit after really bad it's like, you know, especially like no
I don't know everything but you're gonna bring me into the fight. I come I'm coming for blood
Unless they're gonna be nice and respectful like a psyche. Did I say anything disrespectful tonight? I mean go ahead and call me out
Well check
Yeah, yeah anybody call me out. Did I say anything respect disrespectful?
I mean, maybe I did
I've been one too
You know what?
In a million lifetimes, I can never thank God more than I can thank God for my parents my parents are like
Amazing amazing people
I'm sorry to interrupt sorry
made the argument
They were even talked about the money there at the end of it
They made the argument which you my boy said you're eating some fucking food doing his own thing
They made the argument like
Like why would you defend him or whatever? I was like if it was my brother, which I understand we're not brothers
But I was like if it's my brother out there. He was in a fight
It was a 101 then eight people fucking start beating his ass. I would jump in. Yeah, it's eight against you
But fuck it. Let's run it. Uh, and they were tripping out about that
I was like, how do you not like logically? How do you not follow that? It's my brother getting his ass. Well, I'm gonna jump in
Fuck eight against one, but eight against two. I mean fuck. We got a little bit better odds
We're still gonna lose but at least we got some you know
Yeah
Anything that I heard and it's I don't think you would and maybe he was fighting with people of a panel
But he was being attacked on the panel a little bit and so you know what I got goes back to
100% I was attacked
And goes maybe we're not biological blood brothers
That we are brothers. Okay, but don't get it twisted though. Let me not to you but lead to the chat. Oh
You guys aren't that close. We kind of are but like oh, he believes in like terror readings
I just agree with it. We've debated about it
Just because you and your brother like disagree with something or debate something. It doesn't mean you can't fucking get along
Hey, it goes like
Go there
They're very masculine straight guys like families. They try to submit they try to separate us brother
right and then in being beat it you and it's like
unfortunately, like sometimes I feel like
Some people I'm not gonna mention names, but some people are kind of swayed by other people think and things like that
And but you know what?
You know what? I have some people are too weird. I'm not gonna say names
Some people are just too retired to have the conversation. Some people are just easily swayed
Some people like fame even though they're not getting fame you might get like two X like they're not even getting fame
But some people let me make this point though. Some people are just too fucking stupid to even have the conversation
Imagine if they got fame
the
He's not here, but I want you to say what he was saying. You can say what he was saying to Jamie
He's Jamie's like, oh don't touch him a bronze. Jamie also likes to drive. Well, fuck the bronze straight up
First of all, he talked a lot of shit. I know you know bronze time to come join our panel where we don't mute
We don't kick it's free. You know dogs, you know break to us come to come join us. He talked a lot of fucking shit
Bronze was being a bitch night for real and you can clip it and ship it to him right now
They're home. I got you beat up. I didn't see you. Sorry. I
Don't know if it's you
Oh, wait, is it this hole?
Hi
Let's run that bitch dog. Hi, sweetie
You want to run me
All right, so psyche you better take this as a grain of salt when this guy was on my panel for hours
And he just said risk like let's run that bitch
Don't get mad when other people come on my panel and they say
I was on there for like 20 minutes before he
I'm not here for you ghost. I'm here to talk about somebody called you mean
So why is like you and me sitting there in the pad and calling fucking like saying race of shit about fucking bronzeberg?
You know what?
I will donate money if you're gonna have ghosts and trust me. All right
Just giving a suggestion. All right. Yeah, you're gonna leave for
I don't be quiet, but why would you leave? I was just talking you me. I don't leave that's that's pathetic behavior
I know that was fucking crazy. I don't know. No, no, no, no, no, don't let her that was crazy behavior. I
Don't see anything that you me said that was racist. He's a black RG. She wasn't saying
By the way, it's like yeah, I was literally gonna say I'd give you a couple hundred bucks like kick you me right now and let her talk
She's too fucking stupid to realize that I ain't giving nothing now
Like how stupid was that? I was literally gonna agree with her and she fucking left
I wasn't trying to get in the middle be the show and by the way, what's her problem with you me though?
I thought she's like a Japanese
I have no idea
You're rude in the way. I can't see this TV. Hold on. So that's why I'm not letting you on because I haven't seen you on yet
Because the Rudy's right in front of you
You know you're gonna stand as she was talking about black Archie
She's no you don't get to come back here like that. You just
That's what she said I'm gonna send you a screenshot of what she really said what is she what did you say?
I would I would agree with that bronze bird. I don't want to talk to you face-to-face. You're black
Hold on. Oh, she's she's sure about yeah, I know she's sure about
You're gonna believe her over me
No
I was on the panel
I'm talking to you did say you bring to your fucking plate. What are you yelling for what?
Yeah, okay, yeah, I'm looking for the comment
Let me see she said that every single funnel like every single one of my good friends that you ever known and met was because of me
I will tell you me is not one of them. I don't want to fuck without fucking crazy bitch
She said
She said crazy shit in the past
Yeah, I
Already told you who's cool who's not at the end you're like beta. You're right. They were cool to me. They were nice to me
Okay, so I'm gonna give you a choice right now you really think that you're gonna believe me over fucking you me or viva
Yeah, you guys we're gonna talk about everybody on this my panel everybody can call him a scammer call him a fucking grifter
Yes, he actually let people fucking talk to Bronzeberg like that one of my fucking mods that is black
Fuck you and you're fucking you
You are being toxic and you will be back in a couple minutes and you will apologize. Why are you being so toxic? That was crazy
I don't know what I was thinking. I know your sister. So I can't hear your sister bro. Don't give into that. That was crazy
I'm looking right now
She said if she said I come for you payment. She said if you don't do this, I'm gonna do this
How crazy was oh my god, you clip it in the ship it brother. That was fucking crazy
Okay, she's saying he's primitive like maybe even read that's
Yeah, that was you not agree that was crazy well that I couldn't respond that I'm not like able to like you know say one word
I'm not and it's just like she'll scream at me and that's it
You weren't even there she if you don't respond what the person you me said that when you were gone by the way
She said something about being black to Brownsburg
It was like I'm not gonna talk. I don't even know what the fuck that person said that was crazy
She came she talked about running your panel. She just came over and try to do that
She said if you don't do this, I'm gonna do this. That was crazy
Disrespectful she should come over and apologize to be honest with you. I mean, I'll be real with you. She should apologize
Okay, you know what? I
Need apologies like
I don't know. I was fucking crazy
Well, don't come over talking shit though be peaceful that was crazy she never talked shit
If you don't do this psyche, I'm gonna do this. Oh fuck crazy
You know what I'm against racism and I say, you know
You may be worth saying something about race is like that
that's just like it opens you up to be attacked and stuff like that. I know you don't mean it. Do you mean it's a different race than
me, right? You mean it's a different race. It's like we're all different races. All the human race, right?
So I don't know. It's like and I don't want to fight with Bita.
I'm pretty sure this panel is open. I'm pretty sure whoever wants as long as you get along with it can join.
So, Bita.
I'm putting it up. Vita's is running her own show and I don't know why she's like is he...
Did you mean...
Everything, everything else...
Anyone...
Anyone that was just talking about shit about psych fucking joined the panel. Let's run that bitch dog.
Are you okay with that psyche? My bad.
What's your fucking panel by the way? I see that shit all the time. They say I try to run your panel bio
I always say are you okay with that? Are you okay with that? You okay with that? They have nothing to say
Also, you don't keep people up and right now brosberg is here. Do you want to talk to brosberg? Okay?
I want to talk to browns bird. I want some a baby. You don't mind. I'll take some browns
Browns
I mean, I don't
Why do you attack me?
He don't porn bomb or nothing Browns pretty good guy. I don't know if it's a real blog for this problem. Hello
Yo, so y'all talking shit Browns, but you're
No, it's so y'all talking y'all talking shit. What else?
You me are you there? I'm right here
Well, who we talking to you me you me you shit on beaters. I didn't see it
Yeah
I did see a psyche by the way
Are you doubling down
Someone like
What was my first I don't know. Why did you say black? Why did you say black?
Why do you say something about my black skin and turn yeah, honestly after we don't care about anything
You know, this is like he being a scam or whatever. Yeah, we don't care. Why'd you say black? Why did you say that?
When you said it twice, you said to the bottom of it, why did you say I'm going to
address the fuck out? Why'd you say why did you say because he is racist black American? Okay.
So it was racist shit
In all that why was that a point of reference psyche, she's gonna god she lost that one
She's gonna have to answer so you just admitted to being racist on beatest and beatest chat and then came over here and ran your fucking fat mouth
About that grift of fucking psyche, and then you want me to change my opinion.
You come over here being respectful, trying to like fucking help us out, but you're actually
You might be a racist piece of shit, Yard.
You're a racist. You're a racist, you mean.
I agree with that, Yard.
How
You know how you're racing is what you said in the chat
Black skin, why did you say?
And then talk about turn on your camera you black. That's what you said and beat his chat
Why not? All right, it's what letter because you're
All right, so I can we give you me 30 seconds without talking to explainers
You may go ahead. All right
Okay, let me talk
I can't I think because I don't know the manager the the manager more already talking out
So I come up here
And when I heard how to how mr. Braun Braun's birth
And so, with the psyche in front of us, I don't like it, I don't like to hear it.
That's why.
Who's racist first, me, is the psyche, or him?
You're racist runs word that you could I got something to say though hold on a second, bro
You could you know no no no no no no hold on hold on hold on goes come on now you get to know they love
over there
It's not a
Fuck well, let's handle alone. Hey psyche. Let's open up. Let's let's run. Oh, and she's about me
I got myself hold on bro. I want so I don't want her though. I don't want you
Bro, I want some of you to hold on bro
Go ahead
Okay, go ahead
So so like I said, if you felt that way that I was talking about psyche
I've been said that shit about psyche and I don't take back what the fuck I said
Don't give a shit if you let me on panel just now or nothing. You said we should take back a lot of what you said
ghost while I'm talking
So
Shut the fuck up while I'm talking ghost
So so when it comes to you me you could have kept it at me talking shit about psyche
Which I did and I don't take back shit. I said I meant every word I said you made a mention about me
Twice the thing
You wanted to be on some racist shit, we called you out and then you lie. Yeah, you mean you are a racist
over here on psyches where it was saved
Yeah, you mean you're gonna have to
Cause psyche could have sat there and said the same shit he said about yeah
We didn't know you mean it's racist she's not racist she should be here
She's racist. I know
Psyche she kind of is really i'm like a lot
I can't tell you this is psyche just because
Because the MPF like monkey drama try to control his channel his panel in and
Fuck you are
They did to my fans
And I'm gonna keep
And now you want to talk about me being black you racist piece of shit you cunt
Yeah, I don't think that's a good argument. You wanted psyche real quick. Yeah, go ahead
Between me and you I don't think that's a good argument. You want to have on your show because they're talking about race
I will say one pushback, you know, I don't like bronze, but he had a good pushback
She brought up the race first. She said black
Yumi did say that
and I don't think he's really that offended as he's ready to be, and it's like, you know what?
It's a TOS and shit though.
Yeah, but I get called, I'm on AIDS, I'm a grifter, he's probably a grifter.
Okay, Cracker, do you want me to call you Cracker, do you want me to call the F word?
I mean, I won't do that, but you want me to call you Cracker?
You can, you're one too.
I don't like Brunsford, but you can understand why he's offended.
Right?
Right if you meet all you do is like not don't bring up race. Don't be a brace. They bring up what they're saying
Okay, fair
That's fair. You meet well
Yellow
You like to be called yellow you like to be called yellow
I was okay.
You like to go chink?
What team why did you say black? Why do you think that was okay to say that why?
that motherfucker's retarded
No, bitch, no, no, no, you're not gonna talk over me actually we're gonna actually handle this because for one time
I know you're not used to it. Why did you call him black?
Why?
Because he was asking like a black American.
Well, SBA.
Is that wrong?
I don't know.
Chink gets it wrong.
OK.
I'm ending it.